<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Expertise on Entwine Centre</title>
    <link>/expertise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Expertise on Entwine Centre</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ie</language>
    <copyright>site developed using customised [Educenter-Hugo](https://themes.gohugo.io/educenter-hugo/) theme</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 15:27:17 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/expertise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Edge Computing</title>
      <link>/expertise/edge_computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 15:27:17 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/expertise/edge_computing/</guid>
      <description>Edge systems Hardware at the network edge provides an intermediate location for processing to occur between the servers in the cloud and the end device, be it sensor or actuator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/expertise/machine_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/expertise/machine_learning/</guid>
      <description>ML techniques can be used not just to process the data sets generated by the Internet of Things, but also to manage the IoT, to detect intrusions and other anomalies, and to optimise many aspects of IoT design, such as hardware location, spectrum usage optimisation and the minimisation of power consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Infrastructure</title>
      <link>/expertise/network_infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/expertise/network_infrastructure/</guid>
      <description>The Internet of Things places new demands on network infrastructure and requires new solutions that address such distinctive features of IoT as the vast number of nodes, the huge amounts of data collected from leaf nodes of typically low bit rate, the novel network management issues that arise, and the need to support novel paradigms such as edge computing and edge networking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy and Security</title>
      <link>/expertise/privacy_security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/expertise/privacy_security/</guid>
      <description>Security Computer security has become a concern of everyone, and not just of the information and communications technology (ICT) community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensing and Actuation</title>
      <link>/expertise/sensing_actuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/expertise/sensing_actuation/</guid>
      <description>IoT applications often need to interface to the real world to collect data central to informing decisions, which in turn result in physical interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainability</title>
      <link>/expertise/sustainability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/expertise/sustainability/</guid>
      <description>Sustainability in the Internet of Things requires addressing two concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
